<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE pkgmetadata SYSTEM "https://www.gentoo.org/dtd/metadata.dtd">
<pkgmetadata>
  <maintainer type="person">
    <email>rafael.palomar@ous-research.no</email>
    <description>Primary maintainer</description>
  </maintainer>
  <longdescription>
    CTKAppLauncherLib is a free, open-source library that provides support for launching and managing applications on a variety of platforms. It is designed to simplify and streamline the process of launching and managing applications, especially those in the medical imaging and surgical navigation domains.

    The library includes a range of features and modules for launching and managing applications, including support for command-line arguments, environment variables, and application dependencies. It also includes support for a range of platforms, including Windows, macOS, and Linux, as well as integration with other popular medical imaging and surgical navigation tools.

    CTKAppLauncherLib is built on top of the Common Toolkit (CTK), a collection of libraries and tools for medical imaging research and development. It provides access to a range of advanced features and algorithms for medical image analysis and visualization, as well as a highly customizable and extensible architecture for launching and managing applications.

    The library has a user-friendly interface that supports both novice and advanced users, with features such as interactive documentation, code examples, and tutorials. It also includes a range of advanced features for power users, including support for scripting, logging, and application profiling.

    Overall, CTKAppLauncherLib is a powerful and versatile tool for launching and managing applications in the medical imaging and surgical navigation domains, with a strong user community and ongoing development support.
  </longdescription>
  <upstream>
    <remote-id type="github">commontk/AppLauncher</remote-id>
    <bugs-to>https://github.com/commontk/APPLauncher/issues</bugs-to>
  </upstream>
</pkgmetadata>
